<lore>
	<follower name="Shadow" class="mage">
		<origin>
			<p>Shadow used to adventure with Kriv, Kimoto, Amithirsty and the rest before he retired
				to serve as headmaster at the magical academy in Kamiak. He has served there for almost
				a year, assisting in research and administering to the students there.</p>
			<p>Shadow is a halfling mage specializing in conjuration and fire magics.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Roscoe" class="mage">
		<origin>
			<p>Before the Great Century War, Roscoe was a young prodigy trained by Master
				Septain, the same wizard who trained Wildlovelies. He and Lovelies fled
				the Capitol University For Arcane Arts together, but they were separated
				in the woods before Wildlovelies came to Tychicus.</p>
			<p>When a ransom note was sent to Wildlovelies, He and Balasaar massacred a
				tribe of Lychen soldiers in a desert canyon. They found their leader trying
				to summon a demon to posses him. Swift action led to a free Roscoe,
				happily united with his adopted older brother.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Donnar the Grizzled" class="mage">
		<origin>
			<p> An old human wizard originally hailing from the province
				of Cassalua. </p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Mattemeo" class="Assassin">
		<origin>
			<p>The young human male Mattemeo is current master of the ninja dojo
				at Mt. Ebal. When he is not abroad on scouting and wetwork missions,
				he spends his time honing the skills of the assassins who live on 
				the mountain.</p>
			<p>Mattemeo has been fearless since he was first found by [cassie's Character]
				in Month 1. He was attempting to save himself and his mother from a small
				squad of bandits who showed impending attempt at harming them. [cassie's
				character] swiftly saved the both of them.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Rex" class="Assassin">
		<origin>
			<p>Rex is a human assassin who was captured by bandits before being freed by Kriv, Marindred
				Balasaar, et al. His face is covered in scars, and his voice is rather
				gravely. He is a man of few words and he tends to prefer simple solutions
				to tactical problems.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Hess" class="Assassin">
		<origin>
			<p>Hess served a bandit king as his chief assassin. His perfered weapon is a magical 
				garrotte that silences its victim. He was about to use it on Kriv before Marindred
				did his best to diffuse the situation. Hess was curious about God and Jesus, while his
				king took a more violent reaction. Hess has since served with the Guild of Heroes saving
				innocent people, researching new weapon technology and studying the person of Christ
				with Marindred.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Larko" class="Assassin">
		<origin>
			<p>Once talked a renowned criminal into taking a bite of a mysterious apple.
				[If anyone can expound upon this, please let Mike know]</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Radifen" class="Leader">
		<origin>
			<p>Radifen was the governor of Ramoth since its founding just after
				the breakout of the Great Century War (Month -3). He worked closely
				with the heroes of old, giving them quests and assisting with the
				politics of nation since its founding. He currently holds the chief
				seat on the Tychicus council.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Desaric" class="Leader">
		<origin>
			<p>The soft-spoken, concise governor of Mt. Ebal is Desaric.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Kardin" class="Leader">
		<origin>
			<p>Before the formation of Tychicus, Kardin was the governor of the 
				city-state of Kedesh. He loaned his giant raccoon to Kimoto during
				the battle for formation, and later taught Kimoto to wrangle
				giant raccoons as well. Since the formation of Tychicus, he has
				been a shining light for all of Tychicus. He has helped found
				towns, raised employment, and arbitrated disputes with wisdom
				and diligence.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Corinc" class="Leader">
		<origin>
			<p>Before the formation of Tychicus, Corinc was the governor of the 
				city-state of Kamiak. While he made the safe call to not support
				the independance war very much, he has since made up for this
				shortcoming of supprt in his activities since then. He is a very
				peaceful and compassionate leader who values his citizens above
				all else.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Wunk" class="assassin">
		<origin>
			<p>Wunk is a large bladeling trained as a Warblade in the army of Razorin.
				His education is mostly in the martial arts, and he has little other
				intellectual interests. Wunk's speech tends to be monosyllabic, and
				his poetry is equally abysmal. The most important thing in the 
				world to Wunk is his pink, fluffy teddybear which he leaves at home
				when he goes on missions.</p>
			<p>Wunk was trained as a fighter, and his classification as an assassin
				is a bit of a misnomer. As an assassin, he's a bit of a blunt instrument,
				well-adapted for large-scale sabotage or simple-instruction missions.</p>
			<p>During Month 11, one of Razorin's Field Marshalls led a deep strike into
				a mine in Assembly Territory. Field Marshall Maizaka ordered Wunk to 
				assist the Tychean heroes and act as a goodwill liason.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
	<follower name="Torrin Razorback" class="assassin">
		<origin>
			<p> Torrin is an aged Dragonborn who used to be a thief, but has
				since improved his ways... to killing things for the good
				of the nation.</p>
		</origin>
	</follower>
</lore>