<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root>
<contract title="Tick Tick" roll="8"><prompt>
			Continue Research at the arcane College on time-delay detonation packages.
			Specifically ones that are a little less gargantuan.
		</prompt><followers>Remera and Lorani, Roscoe, </followers></contract><contract title="Hammer Time" roll="7"><prompt>
			Begin research on improving Kriv's hammer to have gravity-modulating effects.
		</prompt><followers>Shadow, </followers></contract><contract title="It's Called a what?" roll="7"><prompt>
			Begin research on the non-detection cloak.
		</prompt><followers>Dexter, </followers></contract><contract title="Now You Don't" roll="7"><prompt>
			Continue Research at the arcane College the Invisibility cloaks. A longer duration would be nice.
		</prompt><followers>Gregory, </followers></contract><contract title="Going Green" roll="8"><prompt>
			The UGK has entered an uneasy alliance with us. Let's see if that alliance could include some trade agreements.
		</prompt><followers>Corinc, </followers></contract><contract title="Settle The Scorched Lands" roll="4"><prompt> The lands that the fire titan Coeus used to occupy now belongs to Tychicus,
			but no permanent Tychian establishment exists on Tychicus. In Jaroarfor, Villages must
			be built before towns. Towns before military camps or cities. Cities before forts. </prompt><followers>Desaric, </followers></contract><contract title="The Corriolis Effect" roll="8"><prompt>Go to the Ninja Dojo and begin research on very long range 
			crossbows!</prompt><followers>Mattemeo, </followers></contract><contract title="Scout The Aviary" roll="75"><prompt>Our northern neighbors are enigmatic at the moment. Let's see what
			they're up to.</prompt><followers>Rex, Fai, Evynne, Rorre, Gardonazorph, Stasi, Aramil, </followers></contract><contract title="Scout The Assembly" roll="9"><prompt>In Jaroarfor, our southern border is dominated by a race of sentient
			arcanic constructs, or so the rumor goes. The tribe of Razorin says that they're
			quite unfriendly. Let's see if the rumors are true.</prompt><followers>Hess, Larko, </followers></contract><contract title="Construct the Temple" roll="17"><prompt>The Country needs a center for it's clerics and paladins. Also, a monument to the 
			diety got us this far is well in order. Select a construction site and get building!
			(the player that takes this contract first chooses what city it's built in).
			</prompt><followers>Suuth, Kimoto, </followers></contract><contract title="Construct the Theater" roll="18"><prompt>A center for Bards to hang out would be ideal as well. Grab some nails and
			a planks of wood and get started. (The first player who takes this contract will
			decide which city to build it in).
			</prompt><followers>Marindred, </followers></contract><contract title="Interrogate Enemy" roll="69"><prompt>During his solo op in Gnomerigon, Geoff captured an enemy assassin with
			likley ties to the an enemy assassin's guild. The prisoner could have very valuable
			information. Or she might try to break out and kill everyone. Should be interesting.
			It should be noted that the assassin is wanted in Gnomerigon for committing a massacre.
			If we keep holding her, they might not like that we stole her away.
			</prompt><followers>Balasaar, Kriv, Treklor, Heiam, Geoff, Wildlovelies, </followers></contract><contract title="Scout The Aviary" roll="60"><prompt>Our northern neighbors are enigmatic at the moment. Let's see what
			they're up to.</prompt><followers>Rex, Fai, Evynne, Rorre, Gardonazorph, Stasi, Aramil, </followers></contract></root>
